ILR School Librarian's Office Files /4004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Library, NYSSILR Finance Budget Discussion, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Library, NYSSILR Finance Budget Discussions - 1952 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Library, NYSSILR C-20 Personnel Records Graduate Assistants, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Library, NYSSILR Library Staff Memoranda 1954-57, 1954-1957 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Library, NYSSILR Library Staff Memoranda 1958 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Library Staff Memoranda, 1961-1969 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Personnel - Miscellaneous, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Applications - Part-time and Temporary, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Applications - Professional Positions, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Applications - Circulation Lib. Pos., 1953 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Applications - Clerical Positions, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Library, NYSSILR Applications - Reference Librarian Position, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Applications - Assistant Catalog Position Reference Position, 1956-1969 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Personnel Applications-Reference Librarian Position (Box 9, Folder 16)
  1956
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel (Professional) Job Descriptions and Responsibilities (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel (Clerical) Job Descriptions and Responsibilities, 1954-1956 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records Recommendations, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Recommendations, 1955-1969 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Personnel Jobs Descriptions State University Survey, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Salary and Increments, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Salaries and Increments, 1959-1968 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records Schedules, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Library Work Schedules, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Library Work Schedules, 1955-1967 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records Graduate Assistants, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Graduate Assistants 1955-65, 1955-1965 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Graduate Assistants, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Personnel - Personnel Records Part Time and Temporary, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Library, NYSSILR - Personnel Records - Active Part-Time and Temporary, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Inactive Part-Time and Temporary, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Inactive Personnel Part-Time and Temp. 1960-67, 1960-1967 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Personnel Records - Wage Rates, 1963-1967 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Library, NYSSILR, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Personnel - Wage Rates - Part Time and Temporary, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Personnel - Wage Rates - Part Time and Temporary, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Library Staff Changes 1964-69, 1964-1969 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Active Aaronson, Paula, 1954 (Box 9A, Folder 1)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Adler, S., 1950 (Box 9A, Folder 2)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Active Anthony, C., 1952 (Box 9A, Folder 3)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Active Atwood, Mary, 1953 (Box 9A, Folder 4)
- Personnel Records - Active Barrera, Caroline, 1957-1958 (Box 9A, Folder 5)
- NYSSILR Personnel Records - Individual Bennett, Myron, 1959 (Box 9A, Folder 6)
- Personnel Records - Individual Bergen, Leonie O., 1962 (Box 9A, Folder 7)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Inactive Bien, Theodora B., 1983 (Box 9A, Folder 8)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records Birdsall, G. M., 1951 (Box 9A, Folder 9)
- Personnel - Individual Bovio, Particia, 1964 (Box 9A, Folder 10)
- Personnel Records - Active Mrs. Marie Burnett, 1956 (Box 9A, Folder 11)
- Personnel Records - Individual Calvert, Bette, 1959 (Box 9A, Folder 12)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Active Campbell, Marie, 1953-1954 (Box 9A, Folder 13)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records Active Carlson, Helen, 1952 (Box 9A, Folder 14)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records Active Caudill, Betty, 1952 (Box 9A, Folder 15)
- Personnel - Individual Chater, Judith, 1958 (Box 9A, Folder 16)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records Active Clark, B. E., 1950 (Box 9A, Folder 17)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records Active Collum, C. H., 1950 (Box 9A, Folder 18)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Inactive Court, J., 1949 (Box 9A, Folder 19)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Active Dewey, S. E., 1950 (Box 9A, Folder 20)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Inactive Dierlam, Maxine, 1948 (Box 9A, Folder 21)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Active Dorr, M. L., 1958 (Box 9A, Folder 22)
- Personnel Records - Individual Duino, Russel A., 1963 (Box 9A, Folder 23)
- Personnel Edwards, Elizabeth, 1956 (Box 9A, Folder 24)
- Personnel - Individual Ellison, Sara, 1960 (Box 9A, Folder 25)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Active Evangelista, Mary Dawson, 1955-1956 (Box 9A, Folder 26)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Active Fellenbaum, Helen, 1954-1956 (Box 9A, Folder 27)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Active Mrs. Eleanor Fisher, 1952 (Box 9A, Folder 28)
- Personnel Records - Active Mrs. Greta Fuller, 1956 (Box 9A, Folder 29)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Inactive Graves, E., 1949 (Box 9A, Folder 30)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Inactive Gray, C., 1950 (Box 9A, Folder 31)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Inactive Gray, R., 1949 (Box 9A, Folder 32)
- Personnel - Individual Halpern, Judy, 1959 (Box 9A, Folder 33)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel - Mrs. Rosemary Hempstead, 1953 (Box 9A, Folder 34)
- Personnel - Applications, Professional Horowitz, Martin, 1956 (Box 9A, Folder 35)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Active Mrs. Alicia Hunt, 1952 (Box 9A, Folder 36)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Inactive Jennings, Anne, 1949 (Box 9A, Folder 37)
- Personnel Records - Individual Jeffrey, Newman, 1961 (Box 9A, Folder 38)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Inactive Joseph, Judith, 1949 (Box 9A, Folder 39)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Active Kaimer, Joan, 1952 (Box 9A, Folder 40)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Active Keiser, Miss Marijane, 1955 (Box 9A, Folder 41)
- Personnel Records - Active Miss Elizabeth Knox, 1958 (Box 9A, Folder 42)
- Personnel Records - Active Leach, Ethel R. (Mrs.), 1957 (Box 9A, Folder 43)
- Personnel Records - Active Luce, Ellen, 1957 (Box 9A, Folder 44)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Active Richard Lyon, 1951 (Box 9A, Folder 45)
- Personnel Records - Active Mahany, Paul, 1956 (Box 9A, Folder 46)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Active Matychak, Eleanor, 1955 (Box 9A, Folder 47)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel - Inactive Mizener, Rosemary, 1958 (Box 9A, Folder 48)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Active Nance, Marjorie, 1953 (Box 9A, Folder 49)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Active Nesbitt, M.J., 1949 (Box 9A, Folder 50)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Active Norton, Mrs. Shirley, 1954 (Box 9A, Folder 51)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Active O'Dell, Althea, 1949 (Box 9A, Folder 52)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records Active Hans E. Panofsky, 1961 (Box 9A, Folder 53)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel (Inactive) Mrs. Janice Parsons, 1953 (Box 9A, Folder 54)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Active Mrs. Lillian C. Payne, 1952 (Box 9A, Folder 55)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records Active Pinkos, B., 1955 (Box 9A, Folder 56)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Inactive Pommer, B., 1949 (Box 9A, Folder 57)
- Personnel - Individual Quinn, Phyllis, 1959 (Box 9A, Folder 58)
- Gertrude Rahn, 1955 (Box 9A, Folder 59)
- Personnel Records - Individual Reitkopp, Ellen, 1961 (Box 9A, Folder 60)
- Personnel Records - Active Robbs, Juanita, 1957 (Box 9A, Folder 61)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Active Ross, P., 1950 (Box 9A, Folder 62)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Active Rothman, Roxanne, 1958 (Box 9A, Folder 63)
- Personnel - Individual Rushforth, Nancy Edelman, 1951-1957 (Box 9A, Folder 64)
- Personnel Records - Active Gerald Rounds, 1956 (Box 9A, Folder 65)
- Personnel Records - Active St. John, Iva, 1956 (Box 9A, Folder 66)
- Personnel Scuitto, Jacqueline, 1955 (Box 9A, Folder 67)
- Personnel Records - Individual Saxton, Joan (Miss), 1960 (Box 9A, Folder 68)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Active Shaw, I. B., 1961 (Box 9A, Folder 69)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records Sheary, Mary F. (Box 9A, Folder 70)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Active Simon, Robert, 1956 (Box 9A, Folder 71)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Active Smith, Adrienne, 1956 (Box 9A, Folder 72)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Inactive Spinney, Katherine R., 1959 (Box 9A, Folder 73)
- Personnel Records 0 Inactive Nancy Storck, 1956 (Box 9A, Folder 74)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Active Storr, B. Rhoda, 1956 (Box 9A, Folder 75)
- Personnel - Individual Stucki, Curtis W., 1963 (Box 9A, Folder 76)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Active Mary Swarthout, 1956 (Box 9A, Folder 77)
- Personnel - Active Taylor, Vail (Mrs.), 1957 (Box 9A, Folder 78)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Active Testut, Joanne, 1956 (Box 9A, Folder 79)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Inactive Thomas, Anne E., 1950 (Box 9A, Folder 80)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Active Wallace, Virginia, 1950 (Box 9A, Folder 81)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records Inactive Walsh, Joan, 1956 (Box 9A, Folder 82)
- Personnel Records - Individual Welch, Linda, 1961 (Box 9A, Folder 83)
- Personnel Records - Individual Brellochs, Jacqueline, 1964 (Box 9A, Folder 84)
- Personnel Records - Individual Brookhouse, Sharon, 1969 (Box 9A, Folder 85)
- Personnel Records - Individual Bunkowski, Helena, 1968 (Box 9A, Folder 86)
- Personnel Records - Individual Bushaw, Marguerite, 1967 (Box 9A, Folder 87)
- Personnel Record - Individual Connors, William Edward, 1967 (Box 9A, Folder 88)
- Personnel Records - Individual Crowley, Bonnie, 1968 (Box 9A, Folder 89)
- Personnel Records - Individual Donlon Marey Helen, 1959 (Box 9A, Folder 90)
- Personnel Records - Individual Foster, Shirley F., 1966 (Box 9A, Folder 91)
- Personnel Records - Individual Gelerinter, Mrs. Pearl, 1966 (Box 9A, Folder 92)
- Personnel Records - Individual Golay, Mrs. Michal Ann, 1965 (Box 9A, Folder 93)
- Personnel Records - Individual Grindal, P. Eileen, 1968 (Box 9A, Folder 94)
- Personnel Holloway, Gordon, 1969 (Box 9A, Folder 95)
- Personnel Records - Individual Honness, Marie, 1967 (Box 9A, Folder 96)
- Personnel Records - Individual Hovanus, Emogene S., 1955 (Box 9A, Folder 97)
- Personnel Records - Individual Hubbell, Bertha, 1962 (Box 9A, Folder 98)
- Personnel Records - Individual Jones, Janet, 1967 (Box 9A, Folder 99)
- Personnel Records - Individual Jones, Samuel Milton, 1957 (Box 9A, Folder 100)
- Personnel Records - Individual Keyser, Janine, 1958 (Box 9A, Folder 101)
- Personnel Records - Individual Lillie, Barbara, 1955 (Box 9A, Folder 102)
- Personnel Records, Active Mason, Richard, 1963 (Box 9A, Folder 103)
- Personnel Records - Individual Mick, Roberta, 1956 (Box 9A, Folder 104)
- Personnel Records - Individual Moll, Gertrude, 1962 (Box 9A, Folder 105)
- Personnel Records - Individual Nott, Judith, 1965 (Box 9A, Folder 106)
- Personnel Records - Individual Odza, Rita, 1967 (Box 9A, Folder 107)
- Personnel Records - Individual Palmer, Joyce, 1962 (Box 9A, Folder 108)
- Personnel Records - Individual Pascavage, Shirley, 1965 (Box 9A, Folder 109)
- David Pepth, 1971 (Box 9A, Folder 110)
- Personnel - Individual Patricola, Marilyn, 1950 (Box 9A, Folder 111)
- Personnel - Individual Powers, Sylvia, 1964 (Box 9A, Folder 112)
- Personnel Records - Individual Putzig, Gisela, 1965 (Box 9A, Folder 113)
- Personnel Records - Individual Rykbost, Caroline, 1962 (Box 9A, Folder 114)
- Personnel Records - Active Skiff, Darlene, 1963 (Box 9A, Folder 115)
- Personnel Records - Individual Spinks, Geoffrey, 1963 (Box 9A, Folder 116)
- Personnel - Individual Wilkinson, Ann, 1964 (Box 9A, Folder 117)
- Personnel - Individual Worden, Karen A., 1964 (Box 9A, Folder 118)
- Library, NYSSILR Picnic 1950-55, 1950-1955 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Library, NYSSILR Picnic 1957 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Ira Blank (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Personnel Records - Individual Bowler, Michael, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Personnel Records - Individual Bradley, Breda, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Coleman, Gould, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Personnel Records - Individual Doerrer, David, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Personnel Records - Individual Eckert, Leone, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Personnel Records - Individual Fehring, Maria, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Personnel Records - Individual Freilicher, Miriam, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Personnel - Individual Frick, Elizabeth, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Goodnow, Edith, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Personnel Record - Indiv. Kikuchi, J. Kimiyo, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Mann, Ann, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Mason, Karen, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Library Lists Minnesota, University of Reports on Management Development, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Personnel Records Miller, J. Gormly, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Personnel Records - Individual Naas, Bernard G., 1983 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Personnel - Individual Reino, Cecilia, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Roberts, Kathleen, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Personnel - Individual Roberts, Kathleen, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Personnel Records - Individual Sakr, C. S., 1970 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Personnel Records - Individual Snyder, Sharron, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Personnel Records - Individual Tompsett, Sally, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Personnel Records - Individual Latier, Linda Young, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Personnel - Individual White, Gladys W., 1963 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Actives Yengo, Carmine A., 1956 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Library, NYSSILR Personnel Records - Active Yengo, Margaret, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information Jan. - Apr. 1954 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- ILR 391, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Ref. Letters No. 65314, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- NYSSILR J. G. Miller, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Memorandum, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Library, NYSSILR C-35 Publications General (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Photocopying Service, 1954-1960 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Library, NYSSILR Faculty Carrels, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information May - August 1954 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information September = December 1954 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information Q-S, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information T-Z, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information I-L, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information M-P, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information A-D, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information E-H, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Public Information A-D, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Public Information E-H, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- Public Information I-L, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Public Information M-Q, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Public Information R-T, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Public Information U-Z, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Public Information M-Q, 1957-1958 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Public Information R-T, 1957-1958 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Public Information U-Z, 1957-1958 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Public Information A-D, 1957-1958 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Public Information E-H, 1957-1958 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Public Information I-L, 1957-1958 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information A-D, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information E-H, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information I-L, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information M-Q, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information R-T, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information U-Z, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information A-D, 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, E-H, 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, E-H, 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, I-L, 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, M-Q, 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, R-T, 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, U-Z, 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, A-D, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, E-H, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, I-L, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information M-Q, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information R-T, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information U-Z, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information A-D, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, E-H, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, E-H, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, M-Q, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, R-T, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, U-Z, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, A-D, 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, E-H, 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, I-L, 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, M-Q, 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, R-T, 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, U-Z, 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, A-D, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 41)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, E-H, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, I-L, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 43)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, M-Q, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, R-T, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 45)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information U-Z, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 46)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, A-D, 1964-1967 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, E-H, 1964-1967 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, I-L, 1964-1967 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, M-Q, 1964-1967 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, R-T, 1964-1967 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, 1964-1967 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, U-Z, 1964-1967 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, A-D, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, E-H, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, I-L, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, M-Q, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information, R-T, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Library, NYSSILR Public Information U-Z, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Old Expense Accts., 1968-1970 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Library, NYSSILR Extension General, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Library, NYSSILR Extension Correspondence, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Library, NYSSILR Extension Records - State Library Requests, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Library, NYSSILR Extension Inventories - New York State Library, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Library, NYSSILR Extension Inventories - New York State Library, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Catalog Unit - Memoranda and Correspondence, 1959-1965 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Library, NYSSILR Intra School Loans Records, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Library, NYSSILR Labor-Management Documentation Center Memoranda and Correspondence, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- CMDC Memos and Correspondence, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Library, NYSSILR Advisory Committee, 1956-1960 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Library, NYSSILR Labor-Management Documentation Center Field Trip, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Library, NYSSILR - Field Trips, 1955-1970 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Library, NYSSILR Foreign Exchange Program - Guides and Lists, 1955-1960 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Library, NYSSILR Labor-Management Documentation Reports, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- LMDC Memos v. Correspondence, 1955-1969 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- C-58, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- C-58, 1954-1958 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Reference Correspondence, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- R. Duimo - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Projects Bibliographies (unpublished), 1941-1943 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Projects, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Projects - Guide to Information on Union-Management Relations, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Projects Guide to Information on Union-Management Relations, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Projects Guide to Information on Union-Management Relations, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Projects Guide to Information on Union-Management Relations, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Projects Guide to Information on Union-Management Relations, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Library, NYSSILR, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Projects Local Union Canvass - 1948 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Projects Local Union Canvass - Questionnaires, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Projects Local Union Canvass - Questionnaires, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Projects Local Union Canvass, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Projects Local Union Canvass, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Projects, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Projects Local Union Canvass, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Projects Local Union Canvass, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Projects Local Union Canvass, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Projects Local Union Canvass, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Projects Local Union Canvass, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Projects Local Union Canvass - Questionnaires, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Projects Foreign Labor Materials (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Projects Visual Aids (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Projects Visual Aids Memoranda, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Library, NYSSILR Audio-Visual Aids Correspondence - Association Films, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Library, NYSSILR Audio-Visual Aids Records, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Library, NYSSILR Exhibits, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Libraries and Librarians American Library Association, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Libraries and Librarians Columbia University, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Libraries and Librarians Cornell University Library, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Libraries and Librarians Council on Library Resources, Inc., 1971 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Libraries and Librarians Drexel Institute of Technology (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Libraries and Librarians Illinois State Library, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Libraries and Librarians Illinois, University of, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Libraries and Librarians International Labour Office Library (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Libraries and Librarians Industrial Relations Analysis Library, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Libraries and Librarians Library of Congress, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Libraries and Librarians The New York Library Association, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Libraries and Librarians New York State Library (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Libraries and Librarians Princeton University Library (Box 14, Folder 10)